Lisa Sunhwa Han

Software Engineer

650-713-9833 / ellesis@gmail.com / https://lisa7h.com / Palo Alto, CA, USA

SUMMARY

An experienced software engineer with over 13 years of expertise in building responsive websites and interactive features using JavaScript, node.js, and python. I exhibit technical proficiency, being diligent, and highly organized, have friendly and work well in a team, and possess exceptional problem-solving abilities.

SKILLS

- Language: JavaScript(ES5 and ES6+), TypeScript, Python, HTML5, CSS(flex, Grid), Sass(Scss), Stylus, Pug, BASH, C, C++, C#, Java, PHP
- Frontend: React.js, Next.js, Vue.js, Angular.js, Apollo, GraphQL, Prisma, React Native, Redux, D3.js, Axios, AJAX, Gatsby, TailwindCss, Bootstrap, Material UI, JQuery, Google maps, npm, webpack, Cypress
- Backend: Node.js, Flask, FastAPI, nginx, Java Spring
- Database: PostgreSQL, MySQL, Redis, Oracle, Firebase, Supabase, MongoDB
- Cloud: AWS, Google Cloud, Heroku, Netlify
- Tools: Git, SVN, Docker, Photoshop

PORTFOLIO PROJECTS

- <u>Iyntour.com</u>: Tourism information website based on bloggers' input
 Next.js, Apollo, GraphQL, Tailwind CSS, Material UI-5, Javascript ES6+, CSS, HTML, webpack, npm,
 Responsive design
- amarket.vercel.app: Shopping Site with <u>fakestoreapi</u>
 React, Next.js, Next-Auth.js, Tailwindcss(CSS), Firebase, Javascript ES6+, HTML, webpack, npm
- 3. movie-matcher.lisa7h.com | Github: Movie Matcher Using yts.mx free REST API of the Movie info, React, Redux, Axios, Javascript, HTML, CSS, webpack, npm
- 4. yokose.lisa7h.com | Github: stock and financial index information and notification system React, Redux, Axios, Javascript, HTML, CSS, E-Charts

PROFESSIONAL EXPERIENCE

Software Engineer / FleetUp, San Jose, USA

Feb 2019 ~ Nov 2022

- The Fleet Management system App implemented new features, created an admin dashboard of devices, and maintained the daily operation: sortable data table system and implemented new device types such as dashcams and air filters and improved fleet tracking UI on the google map, AI-Dashcam report generate, annotation system and risk event mailing system
- Implemented internal solutions: Billing and revenue tracking solution(Statistics user billings, Export Billing Details excel Report), Customer service tracking solution(Marketing solution, Statistics Customer Usage, and Summary Report), Device activation and assignment solution(Account search list, Assignment History, VIN Decoder, Cable Auto Suggestion). Lambda API Optimization.
- Designed and implemented RESTful web service APIs and algorithms for Business Intelligence utilizing
- JavaScript, Angular.js, React.js, Vue.js, Axios, AJAX, CSS(flex), Sass(Scss), Stylus, Pug, Bootstrap, jQuery, DataTables, jqGrid, EasyUI Library, Google map, Node.js, Java maven, JSP, Java Spring, Oracle DB, Tomcat Apache, AWS

Software Engineer (Intern) / Wisen.space, Palo Alto, USA

Oct 2018 ~ Feb 2019

- Develop the functionality for kids' educational coding practice web solutions.
- Built a chatting system for teachers and students with node.js web socket.
- JavaScript(ES6+), Node.js, CSS, MongoDB, Git, RDMS RESTful API

US Green Card Process

2015 ~ 2018

Waited as a dependant while my spouse was in the process

Software Engineer / Merlion Software, Vancouver, Canada

Apr 2009 ~ Dec 2012

• Designed and developed several architectural web applications in collaboration with the architectural software company "Virtual Builders" in South Korea. PHP, Javascript, jQuery, Codelgnitor, MySQL

Software Engineer / Youl Systems, South Korea

Aug 2003 ~ July 2005

- Developed and maintained the Digital Library System of KEPCO (Korea Electric Power Corporation)
 with Javascript, ASP, COM+, and Visual Basic
- Designed and maintained the Portal System of KEPCO (Windows Server 2003, IIS 6.0, Oracle, ASP)
- Maintained Hummingbird Database and Search Engine 5.1 for KEPCO

Software Engineer / Korea Dotcom, South Korea

Mar 2002 ~ Aug 2003

- Designed and developed Banking Transfer Engine Solution backed with XML and Oracle
- Participated in the upgrade of the integrated repeater management system for Korea Telecom Freetel
- Administered the Korea Dotcom corporate website (Windows server, IIS5.0, MS Exchange Server)

Software Engineer / Daol Soft, South Korea

Feb 2001 ~ Mar 2002

- Developed the extension plugin for the desktop publishing system Quark XTension(Windows and Mac)
- Developed Filegate website (Linux, PHP, and MySQL)
- Created i-yah.com A3 XML Viewer worksheet print program (Windows 2000 server, Tomcat 3.0, JSP, JAVA Beans, XML, and XSL)
- Built ebook contents system from XML/XSL DATA on Linux, Tomcat 3.0, JSP, Java Beans

Software Engineer / Sial Tech, South Korea

Oct 1999 ~ Feb 2001

- Created and maintained corporate and client websites(Windows NT server, Active Perl, CGI, and ASP)
- Implemented Investor Management System with Visual Basic
- Developed the plugin software for Quark XTension on Mac

EDUCATION

2001, Object-Oriented Programming Courses, Joongang IT Engineering Academy, South Korea

2000, Certificate of Completion, Informix Database, Informix Korea, South Korea

1999, Teaching Certificate of Science and Physics, Jeonbuk National University, South Korea

1999, Bachelor of Science in Physics, Jeonbuk National University, South Korea

LANGUAGE SKILLS

English: Fluent / Korean: Native

VISA STATUS / CITIZENSHIP

US green card holder and Canadian citizen.